《法外情真》前情提要
Previously on The Guardian.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
这是你想要的
This is what you want?
你想当爸爸吗
Do you want to be a father?
妈妈的订婚戒指还在你那儿吗
You still have mum's engagement ring?
嗯
Yeah.
可以给我吗
I'd like to have it.
比起婚姻  我们面前有更大的
We have a much bigger decision in front of us now...
- 决定要做  - 我不  如果你不想嫁给我  我不在乎
- then marriage. - I don't... I don't care if you don't want to marry me uh...
没关系的  我只是
It's alright, I just...
我知道我准备好要做一个父亲了
I know that I'm ready to be a father.
关于露露的事儿  我  呃
About lulu, I'm ... uh...
我特别为你高兴
I'm happy as hell for ya.
现在一切事情的发展
I'm just very pleased,
都让我感到非常开心
by the way everything's turning out.
哈西看起来很生气
Hassey looks pissed.
不  他本来看起来就这样
No, it's just the way he looks.
我想让你们亲眼看看
Wanted you to see this for yourselves.
流浪者  非法占有者  毒贩  他们还都在这里
Bums, squatters, drug peddlers, they're all still here.
我将在下周开展200个单位的开发
Now, I'm breaking ground on a 200 unit development next week.
你答应过我你会处理这件事的
You promised me you were gonna take care of this.
我知道  我已经和匹兹堡警察局谈过两次了
I know, and I've spoken to the Pittsburgh Police Department twice already--
好吧  那就再跟他们谈
Well, speak to them again.
我雇你的公司是因为你们可以对付那帮臭警察
I mean, the reason I hired your firm is you represent the damn cops.
我们明白这个问题
We understand the problem, Ron--
我不是想要你明白这个问题  伯顿
I don't want you to understand the problem, Burton.
我是希望你可以解决它
I want you to fix it.
我们现在就去找市政厅的关系  好吗
We'll go down and see our people at the city, right now, okay?
谢谢
Thank you.
谁是负责人
Who's in charge?
谁是这里的负责人
Who's the officer in charge here?
嘿  女士  在这里
Hey, lady! Over here!
爷爷  爷爷
Gramps! Gramps!
放开我  伙计
Get off me, man!
劳里·绍尔特  社会服务中心  我接到了电话
Laurie Solt, Social Services. I got a call.
嗯  这孩子和他祖父就住在这里
Yeah, this kid and his grandpa were living here unlamully.
是在救护车里的那个吗
That the grandfather in the ambulance?
是啊  他们把我们赶出房子之后  他就晕过去了
Yeah! After they threw us out of our house, he collapsed!
他生病了
He's sick.
嘿  现在的地产所有者希望他们可以离开
Hey, the rightful owners wanted them evicted.
我们会知道他们要把你祖父带到哪里去的
We'll find out where they're taking your grandfather.
尼克
Nick.
下午好  你好吗
Good afternoon. How are you?
- 不错  - 挺好
- Fine. - Good.
这是唐尼·隆戈
This is Donnie Longo.
你的公司今天早上把他赶出了家
Your firm threw him out of his home this morning,
和这些大多数剩下的人一样
along with most of the rest of these people.
唐尼
Donnie?
他是你的委托人
He's your client.
收容所听证会  下午2点
Shelter hearing, 2 p.m.
露露分配给我的案子
Lulu assigns my cases.
我和露露谈过了  她说他是你的案子
I talked to Lulu. She said he's yours.
这是你的烂摊子  把他解决完
lt's your mess. Help clean it up.
第三季  第九集
法外真情
翻译   不会吐泡泡   的金鱼
校对  油 球
各位  请坐下来安静一下
Everybody, please, keep it down and have a seat.
我一会就回来
I'll be with you in a moment.
特效  转轮 枪
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
你看  这只是一张驴子的照片
You see, this is just a picture of a donkey.
这对我没用处
This doesn't help me.
各位  请大家注意一下好吗
Uh, everyone, could I have your attention, please?
请稍等一下
Please, just a for minute.
我们正在竭尽全力寻找你们每个人都可以住的的地方
We're doing everything we can to find each of you a place to stay.
只不过需要一些时间  好吗  对此我感到很抱歉
lt's just gonna take some time, okay? I'm sorry about this.
当你们填写完了全部资料  如果有任何问题
When you finish all of your paperwork, if you have any questions
或者有什么我可以帮你们的话  就告诉我
or if there's anything I can do for you, then Iet me know.
脱掉你的上衣
Take off your top.
谢谢  非常感谢
Thank you. Thanks a lot.
那位女士是什么意思
What did that lady mean?
什么
What?
你的烂摊子
''Your mess.''
没什么事
Nothing.
嗯  她说的好像是你把所有人都赶出去了
Well, she said it like you were the guy who threw everybody out.
我没有
I'm not.
但她就是那样说的
But she said it like that.
这儿没什么信息
There's not a lot here.
我从来没有遇到过麻烦
I never been in any trouble.
你上学吗
You go to school?
是啊  埃文代尔高中
Yeah. Avondale High School.
你父母呢
How about your parents?
他们已经死了  那时候我才差不多四岁  听着
They died when I was, like, four. Look...
我不在乎我们住在哪里  我只想和爷爷在一起  好吗
I don't care where we live, I just want to be with Gramps, all right?
我在想办法帮助你
I'm trying to help you.
好吧  但那女人说得好像是你把我们赶出去了
Well, that lady kinda made it sound like you threw us out.
- 唐尼·隆戈  - 是我
-- Donnie Longo? --Yeah.
我是路易莎·阿切尔  我将和你祖父一起工作
I'm Louisa Archer. I'll be working with your grandfather.
好的
Okay.
我现在要去医院看他  你想不想要搭便车
I'm going to see him at the hospital now if you want a ride.
你应该在场
You should be present.
艾比  福克斯下台后
Abby, with Fox stepping down
市议会就没有真正的自由主义了
there's not one true liberal voice left on the City Council.
没有一个人真正了解我们的城市发生了什么
Not one person who truly understands what's happening in our city,
穷人发生了什么
with our poor.
上次竞选时  你就淘汰了
Last time you ran, you got killed.
我在选举中失败了 多了不起啊
I lost an election. Big deal.
你获得了百分之四的选票
You got four percent of the vote.
我那时候才29
I was 29.
没有人比我了解法律
No one has my understanding of the law.
也没有人也没有人像我一样和弱势群体合作过
Or my track record of working with the under-privileged.
但同样也没有相关机构记录过
No one has your track record with the authorities either.
谁会记得那些事情
Who remembers that stum?
如果你要竞选的话 你的对手会记起来的
Your opponents will, if you run.
所以我准备为自己辩护
So I'm prepared to defend myself.
艾比  拜托
Abby, please.
我现在不再管理这个地方了  我有时间了
Now that I don't run this place anymore, I have the time.
我们已经认识很久了  阿尔文  所以我要告诉你
We've known each other a long time, Alvin, so I should tell you.
我倾向于  不要
I'm leaning toward a... no.
你们两位是索尔特女士派来的吗
You two gentlemen sent here by Ms. Solt?
那个好看的老女人
The good-looking older broad?
你们为什么不来我办公室呢
Why don't you guys come on in my office?
所以  我想你需要一个住处
So, I'm assuming you need a place to live.
是的  一个不错的地方
Yeah. Someplace nice.
问题是现在几乎是冬天了  所有好的避难所都满了
Well, the problem is it's almost winter, so all the good shelters are full.
那些不是的  他们的服务对象是未成年人和未婚妈妈
Those that aren't, cater to juveniles, unwed mothers.
休利特公寓怎么样
What about the Hewlett House?
我认识的一个家伙说那里很不错
A guy I know who got in there says it's great.
你不是单单去休利特公寓就好了  你得断毒断酒
You don't just walk into the Hewlett House. You have to be sober.
你必须在住进去两周内找到工作
You have to have a job within two weeks of residency.
你还需要付一些房租
You're required to pay some rent.
那他为什么要先走
So why does he get to go first?
先生  等一下  您为什么不坐下来呢?
I'll be with you in a minute, sir. Why don't you have a seat?
我现在周末打扫停车场  一周60英镑
I sweep parking lots on weekends, make 60 a week.
我已经五个月没有犯瘾了
And I've been clean for five months now.
好吧
All right.
你为什么不填一份申请表  我来看看我能做些什么
Why don't you fill out an application, and I'll see what I can do.
噢  谢谢你  真的非常感谢你
Oh, thank you. Thank you very much.
是啊  超级流浪汉
Yeah! Super Bum!
你也要给我一份休利特公寓的表格吗
You gonna give me one of those Hewlett House forms, too?
应该不是吧
Didn't think so.
全名
Full name?
雷·施米尔  我的朋友们叫我鲁弗斯
Ray Schmiel. My friends call me Rufus.
最高学历  雷
Highest level of education, Ray?
为什么
Why?
我想让你参加一个由政府资助的职业项目
I was gonna try and get you into a county-sponsored vocational program.
好吧  只要给我找到一个地方像杰拉尔德一样就好了
Well, just find me a place like Gerald.
你要清醒一点  你必须要有一份工作
You have to be sober. You have to have a job.
所以  最高学历
So... highest level of education?
哈佛
Harvard.
施米尔先生  你在浪费时间
You're wasting my time, Mr. Schmiel.
好吧  奥尔德里奇高中
All right. Aldrich High School.
什么
What about it?
我的最高学历
My highest level of education.
是吗  你什么时候毕业
Yeah? When did you graduate?
54年
'54.
你认识罗伯特·马斯特森吗
Did you know a Robert Masterson?
- 那是谁  - 我父亲
-- Who's that? -- My dad.
鲍比·马斯特森
Bobby Masterson!
我当然知道他
Sure I knew him.
好人啊  他现在怎么样了
Great guy. How's he doing?
他去世了
He passed away.
哦  太可惜了
Aw. Damn shame.
我们在店里面一起工作了四年
We were in shop together all four years.
他们把我放在那里因为我不是一个非常好的学生  你知道的
They put me in there because I'm not a very good student, you know.
但是你父亲  他真的很好
But your dad? Oh, he was good.
高三时获得最佳项目奖
Won Best Project, senior year.
做了一个猪一样形状的砧板
Made a cutting board shaped like a pig.
- 我的父亲吗  - 是的  他很有才华
-- My dad? -- Yeah. He was talented.
哈哈  世界真小啊  伙计  世界真小
Ha ha! Small world, man. Small world.
嘿  唐尼
Hey, Donnie.
怎么了
What's wrong?
心脏  像往常一样
Oh, the ticker, like usual.
疼不疼
Does it hurt?
是的  有一点
It did, a little.
我现在好多了
I feel good now.
唐尼  医生问我药的事了
Hey, Donnie, the doc asked me about my pills.
我不记得了
I can never remember.
我告诉他你都知道  所以
I told him you know 'em all, so...
他可能在楼下大厅
He's probably down the hall.
去告诉他  好吗
Go tell him, huh?
- 好的  - 好孩子
- Okay. - Good boy.
隆戈先生  我是匹兹堡法律服务部的路易莎·阿切尔
Mr. Longo, I'm Louisa Archer from Legal Services of Pittsburgh.
你是律师
You a lawyer?
是的  如果你愿意  我可以在唐尼的收容所听证会上帮忙
Yes, and if you want, I can help you with Donnie's shelter hearing.
收容所听证会
Shelter hearing?
社会服务有点担心你照顾唐尼的能力
Well, Social Services is concerned about your ability to care for Donnie,
考虑到你的健康和  现在你没有家了
considering your health and...well, now the fact that you have no home.
警察说我不能再待在那里了
The cops said I couldn't stay there anymore.
业主希望您可以离开
The owner wanted you evicted.
为什么是现在
Why now?
我从65年就住在那儿了
I've been there since '65.
你从1965年起就住在那栋房子里了吗
You've been living in that house since 1965?
- 是啊  - 非法占用吗
- Yeah. - Squatting?
不是的  是租房  至少有一段时间是的
No, renting. At least for a while.
我不懂你的意思  你从谁那里租的
I'm not following you. Who were you renting from?
哦  我不记得了  某个家庭吧
Oh, I don't remember. Some family.
他们拥有这块土地上所有的房子
They owned all the homes on the lot.
然后你就不再租房了
And then you stopped renting?
我不再支付费用了
I stopped paying.
为什么
Why?
这些房子本来就不太好
Well, the houses weren't too good to begin with,
而那个家庭  却让它们散架了
and that family, they just let them fall apart.
所以我停止了支付房租
So I stopped paying rent.
那是什么时候
And when was that?
哦  大约在79年
Oh, around '79.
你就一直住在那里
And you just kept living there?
70年代钢铁厂倒闭后  我找不到工作
When the steel mills shut down in the seventies, I couldn't find work.
接下来我就生病了
Then I got sick.
我不打算放弃一个免费的住所
I wasn't about to give up a free home.
我和唐尼会怎么样
What's gonna happen to me and Donnie?
你不会主张违法占有吧
You're not gonna argue adverse possession.
如果隆戈先生可以证明他一直住在那里的话
lf Mr. Longo can prove he's been living on that property
21年没有支付租金
without paying rent, for 21 years--
你要怎么证明这一点
How you gonna prove this?
好吧  如果他说的是真的  那产权就是他的
Well, if what he's saying is true, the property belongs to him.
所以你是在告诉我  如果有人在别人的房子里住得够久的话
So you're telling me that if someone lives on someone else's property long enough
房子就是他们的了
it just becomes theirs?
如果他连续21年住在这里  而业主却什么也没有做
lf he lives on it for 21 consecutive years and the owner does nothing about it.
告诉我他是错的
Tell me he's wrong about this.
好吧  当务之急是要朗格先生证实他说的话
Well, the burden will be on Mr. Longo to prove his claim,
但既然你现在是合法所有人  这在法庭上很有发言权
but since you're currently the legal owner, that'll sit well in court.
合法所有人
Currently the legal owner?
我从县里光明正大地把这处房产买了下来
I bought this property fair and square from the county.
你是在拍卖会上买的  但要付所有的留置权和索赔权
You bought it at auction, subject to all liens and claims,
而且这就是索赔
and this is a claim.
哈西先生  他们只有一个不靠谱的老头说的话
Mr. Hassey, all they have is the word of an unreliable old man.
罗恩  我们需要你签字
Ron? We need you to sign for this.
这个项目每天都被延迟  我就赔钱  你明白吗
And every day this project is delayed, I lose money. You understand that?
我知道
I do.
我可能有点冲突
I may have a conflict here.
怎么会呢
How so?
我代表隆戈先生的孙子出席了他在收容所的听证会
I'm representing Mr. Longo's grandson at his shelter hearing.
又是LSP律所
LSP again.
嗯  我仍然可以为那位委托人工作  露露还没有提交任何文件
Well, I can still work for the client. Lulu hasn't filed anything yet.
- 嗯  她会的  我会和她谈谈的
-- Well, she will. -- I'll talk to her.
看看你能否说服她
See if you can talk some sense into her.
听着  你的生日快到了
Now, listen, uh, your birthday's coming up.
你为什么不跟香农和我在纳马林过个周末呢
Why don't you and Shannon and l spend a weekend at Namacolin?
泡个温泉  做个按摩  放松一下
Hit a spa, get a massage. You know, relax a little bit.
- 按摩吗  - 是啊
-- A massage? -- Yeah.
他们有那种裹泥的东西  不管你叫它什么
They've got that mud-wrapping thing, whatever you call it.
应该效果不错的
lt's supposed to work pretty good.
好吧  我看看我的日程安排
Well, I'll check my schedule.
对你有好处的
Be good for you.
在隆戈康复后  天主教慈善机构有一个机构
Upon Mr. Longo's recovery, Catholic Charities has a facility
目的是让无家可归的家庭团聚
whose goal is to keep homeless families together.
阿彻尔女士  这是专为单身母亲和她们的孩子设计的
Ms. Archer, that facility is designed for single mothers and their children.
没错  但他们的章程里没有否认
Right, but there's nothing in their charter that denies--
索尔特女士  社会服务的立场是什么呢
Ms. Solt, what is Social Services' position?
唐尼·隆戈在照顾一个生病的成年人时  一直生活在可怕的环境中
Donnie Longo has lived in horrible conditions while caring for a sick adult.
在此期间  他半正规地就读于学校
During that time, he's attended school on a semi-regular basis
也没惹麻烦
and kept out of trouble.
想想如果把他放在合适的环境里  他会做什么
lmagine what he'd do if placed in the proper environment.
唐尼做得好是因为他祖父  而不是他
Donnie did well because of his grandfather, not in spite of him.
我们没有理由把他们分开
There's no reason to keep them separate.
我同意
I agree.
你建议他和他祖父一起住在医院吗
Do you suggest he live in the hospital with him?
不  我建议隆戈先生康复后
No, I suggest when Mr. Longo recovers,
所有这些都是为了找到这两个人可以住在一起的地方
all emorts be made to find a facility where these two can live together.
可能吧  但与此同时  他需要一个住的地方
Possibly. But in the meantime, he needs some place to stay.
所以  我把唐纳德安置在阿勒格尼男孩收容所
So, I'm placing Donald in the Allegheny Boys Shelter
直到找到合适的寄养家庭
until a suitable foster family can be found.
如果隆戈先生那时候
lf the time comes where Mr. Longo
有能力为他的孙子提供足够的照顾
is able to provide adequate care for his grandson,
我们会重新讨论这个问题
we will revisit this issue.
阿勒格尼男孩收容所
Allegheny Boys Shelter?
也不是那么糟糕
lt's not so bad.
等一等  我爷爷怎么样  我的意思是
Wait. What about Gramps? I mean...
我需要照顾他  不然他会死在那里的
I need to take care of him. He'll die in that place.
有医生会照顾你的祖父
There are doctors that can take care of your grandfather.
但我知道什么时候给他吃药
But I know when to give him his pills.
我知道该往他的果汁里放多少水  他的胃就不会痛了
I know how much water to put in his juice so his stomach won't hurt.
我需要和他在一起  你得让我跟他回去
I need to be with him. You need to get me back with him.
现在不行  唐尼
lt's not gonna happen right now, Donnie.
跟我走吧  唐尼  我们应该离开了
Come on, Donnie. We should go.
你说过你会让我们在一起的
You said you'd keep us together!
现在  如果拉尔夫·隆戈有一个家或一些钱
Now, if Ralph Longo had a home or some money,
他是可以留在他的孙子身边的
he could stay with his grandson.
争论违法占用权  你不可能胜诉
You're not gonna win on adverse possession,
不是占居者这么说就行的
not based on the word of an illegal squatter.
是的  好吧
Yeah, well...
我得回医院了
I gotta get back to the hospital.
好吧  我们今晚再谈
All right, we'll talk about it tonight.
好的
Yeah, we will.
我要
I'm gonna have the--the...
西冷牛排  七分熟
the New York Strip, medium well,
杰克丹尼
and a Jack...
占边威士忌
Jim Beam.
不  我不会给你买酒的
No, I'm not buying you alcohol.
你父亲也很固执
Your old man was stubborn, too.
固执
Stubborn?
我一直认为他是  呃
I always thought of him as, uh...
我不知道    也许说是平庸吧
I don't know... indifferent.
不  不是的
No. No.
他可以成为任何他想成为的人
He was a real mule when he wanted to be.
有一次  我们有位老师  特伯先生
This one time, we had this teacher, Mr. Turbain.
特伯一直在欺负这个孩子 安迪·布劳纳  因为他结结巴巴的
Turbain was always picking on this kid, Andy Blauner, because he stuttered.
叫他布布布 布劳纳
Called him B-B-B-Blauner.
听起来像个了不起的老师啊
Sounds like a great teacher.
所以有一天  在上课前
So one day, before class,
布劳纳在黑板上写了
Blauner wrote on the board,
特伯是一个胖胖胖胖  胖屁股
''Turbain is a f-f-f-f-fat ass.''
你知道的  写了五次
You know, like with five ''F''s.
所以特伯进来的时候  他非常生气
So Turbain comes in, and he blows his top.
然后拿出了他的戒尺  抓住了布劳纳
And he takes out his paddle, and he grabs Blauner,
把他从座位上推开  推到桌子上去
and he yanks him out of his seat and bends him over the desk.
就在他要被打晕的时候
And just about when he's gonna get whacked,
你的老爸跳起来说
your old man jumps up and he says,
是我干的  胖胖胖胖  胖屁股
''l did it, f-f-f-fat ass.''
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
阿尔文  我能跟你谈一会儿吗
Alvin. Can I talk to you for a minute?
我马上回来
Be right back.
- 你不能和他呆在一起  为什么不能
-- You can't stay in here with him. -- Why not?
他的外表  说实话  还有他身上的臭味
His appearance. And, frankly, his stink.
你是什么  法西斯份子吗
What are you, a fascist?
听着  我不知道那是什么意思  但我不能从酒吧里见到他
Look, I don't know what that means, but I can smell him from the bar.
噢  得了吧  杰瑞  饶了他吧
Oh, come on, Jerry, cut the guy a break.
- 阿尔文  你  - 我们哪儿也不去
- Alvin, you-- - We're not going anywhere.
嘿  伙计  我快死了
Hey, man, I'm dying here.
我得喝一杯
I gotta have a drink.
一杯  就一杯
One, and that's it.
所以你在那里生活的那些年里没有支付租金
So all those years that you lived there without paying rent
法律称这是对真正的财产所有者的不利生活
the law calls that ''living adversely'' to the true property owner.
生活不利
Living adversely?
- 是的  - 那是什么意思
- Right. - What does that mean?
根据定义  它意味着你住在那里
Well, by definition it means that you lived there
以一种开放的  连续的  敌对的方式
in an open, continuous, and hostile manner.
哦  不  我从来没有对任何人怀有敌意
Oh, no, I was never hostile to anybody.
不  这只是一个定义
No, it's just a definition.
重要的是你要知道  你在那里住得够久了
What's important for you to know is that you lived there long enough
久得足以声称产权是你的
to claim that the property is yours.
那房子是我的了吗
The house is mine?
嗯  我们还得让法院同意
Well, we'd have to get the court to agree...
如果你想诉讼的话
if you want to fight.
然后那房子就是我的了
And then the house is mine?
是的
Yes.
那我可以搬回去和唐尼一起住了吗
I could move back there with Donnie?
不是那幢房子
Well, not that house,
但是哈西会支付你土地的钱  然后你就可以买房子了
but Hassey would pay you for the land and then you could buy a home.
给我和唐尼
For me and Donnie?
是的  我想如果你的健康状况得到改善
Well, I think if your health improves
丹尼可能会和你一起生活
there's a chance that Donnie could live with you.
机会有多大
How good a chance?
那我不太清楚
Well, that I don't know.
那我想要打官司  可以吗
I want to fight. Okay?
可以
Okay.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
露露提出了对哈西宣告判决的动议
Lulu filed a motion for declaratory judgment against Hassey.
我以为你会和她谈谈
I thought you were gonna talk to her.
是的  我会的
Well, I did.
嗯  我试过了
Well... I tried.
我还在跟进那个孩子的事  所以我想我不能参与这个案子了
Well, I'm still working with that kid, so I guess I'm off the case.
是啊  还有你和对方律师上床的事
Yeah. That and the fact that you're sleeping with opposing counsel.
是的  我想说  我想说你不需要参与这个案子了
Yeah, I'd say-- I'd say you're off the case.
我会告诉哈西的
I'll tell Hassey.
嘿  露露
Hey, Lulu.
伯顿  你在这里做什么
Burton. What are you doing here?
呃  给你委托人一万美元怎么样
Well, how does $10,000 to your client sound
如果他立即放弃财产索赔
if he drops his property claim immediately?
- 一万美元  - 是的
- $10,000? - Yeah.
伯顿  你不能用令人厌恶的钱来收买我的客户
Burton, you can't buy my client off with a nuisance value.
讨厌吗  在我的家乡  一万美元是一大笔钱啊
Nuisance? Where I come from, $10,000 is a lot of money,
尤其是当一个人运气不好的时候
especially when a man's down on his luck.
我客户的索赔值六位数  而不是五位数
My client's claim is worth mid-six figures, not low fives.
我来问你个问题
Let me ask you something.
你以前处理过逆权占有申索吗
You ever handle a adverse possession claim before?
我不明白这有什么关系
I don't see how that's relevant.
我处理过  相信我
I have, and believe me--
你知道吗什么  我肯定能处理好的
You know what? I'm sure I can handle it.
我相信你可以的
Oh, I'm sure you can.
我只是想确认一下你们是否能接受一个合适的报价
I'd just like to make sure that you recognize a good offer
当它呈现给你的时候
when it's presented to you.
哦 我可以  我只是不认为这是合理的报价
Oh, I can. I just don't think this is one.
如果你把我告上法庭  但你输了
lf you take me to court and you lose,
我不得得向你提出制裁和法律费用
I'm gonna have to hit you with sanctions and legal costs,
我也就不确定这个地方还能不能撑得下去
and I'm not real sure this place could afford it.
你在威胁我吗  伯顿
Are you threatening me, Burton?
不  并不是的
No, not at all.
我只是想让你想一想  仅此而已
I just want you to think about it, that's all.
伯顿
Burton.
我已经考虑过了
I have thought about it.
你的提议被否决了
Your offer's rejected.
哦
Oh.
好吧   保重
Okay. Take care.
嘿
Hey.
我刚刚在LSP那边
I was just over at LSP.
怎么回事
How did it go?
呃  路易莎
Uh, Louisa.
你在那边儿也做不了什么了  孩子
You got your hands full there, son.
是的  我知道
Right. I know.
她对这个财产索赔很认真
She's serious about this claim.
是的
Right.
哈西每天都坐在那块土地上
And every day that Hassey sits on that property,
这花了他几千美元
it costs him thousands of dollars.
嗯  她只是在做她认为最好的事
Well, she's just doing what she thinks is best.
你知道  如果她继续这样做的话
You know, if she moves forward with this,
我要像对待其他对手一样对待她
I'm gonna have to treat her like any other adversary.
你应该这么做
As you should.
我认为这种行为是没有意义的
I'm gonna claim the action is frivolous
要求LSP支付所有的法律成本和损失的收入
and demand LSP pay for all the legal costs and lost revenue.
好
Right.
好吧  不管怎么说  这个家伙  拉尔夫·隆戈
Well, for what it's worth, this guy, Ralph Longo,
他需要的只是一个居住的地方
all he needs is a place to live.
- 嘿  罗恩  - 伯顿
- Hey, Ron. - Burton.
- 你好吗  - 好吧  我们拭目以待
- How you doing? - Well, we'll see.
- 很高兴见到你  - 是啊
- Good to see you. - Yeah.
罗恩  恐怕我儿子不能参与这个案子了
Ron, I'm afraid my son has got to step away from the case.
好吧  你觉得怎么好  就怎么办
Well, whatever you think is best.
那么
So?
我和隆戈的律师谈了谈  她拒绝了我们的提议
So I talked to Longo's attorney, and she turned down our offer.
他拒绝了一万美元
He turned down ten grand?
是啊
Yeah.
伯顿  什么样的流浪汉会拒绝一万美元
Burton, what kind of homeless guy turns down ten grand?
我把钱都花在这件事上了
I am hemorrhaging money on this thing.
我知道  但是我们还有其他的选择
I know that, but we do have other options.
- 比如说  - 好吧  我们可以起诉
- Like what? - Well, we could fight it.
那只会花费很多的钱  浪费很多的时间
That's just gonna cost a lot of money, waste a lot of time.
或者我们可以再报一次价
Or we could make a different offer.
- 更多的钱  - 不行
- Of more money? - No.
这家伙想要的只是一个家  和  呃
All this guy wants is a home, and, uh...
而你碰巧有几千个公寓  所以
and you happen to have several thousand, so--
你想让我给这个家伙一个吗
You want me to give this guy one of my units?
不需要太好的  但我想这样就行了
It doesn't have to be fancy, but I think that might do it.
这样所有的麻烦都可以解决了吗
And that would make this whole mess go away?
我是那么认为的
I think so.
做生意的另一个成本
Another cost of doing business.
让我们解决它吧
Let's just get it done.
好吧  罗恩  我会随时通知你的
Okay, Ron. I'll keep you posted.
- 很高兴见到你  - 我也是
- Good to see you. - You, too.
嘿  我要早点回家  我觉得不太舒服
Hey, I'm gonna go home a little early. I'm not feeling too well.
- 好的  - 我很抱歉
- Okay. - Sorry.
没关系  你的活我可以替你做
No, I can cover for you.
好的  谢谢你
All right. Thanks.
你怀孕多长时间了
How far along are you?
呃  只有六个星期
Uh, just six weeks.
尼克的吗
Nick's?
当然是的
Of course.
嗯  我认为这很好
Well, I think that's great.
谢谢
Thank you.
你会成为一个好妈妈的
You're gonna be a wonderful mother.
谢谢你
Thank you.
所以  呃  你有什么计划
So, uh, what are your plans?
什么意思
What do you mean?
关于工作  你的工作计划
About work. Work plans.
一如既往地  只是  你知道的  工作
Same as always, just... you know, to work.
- 好的  - 为什么这么问
- Okay. - Why?
嗯  如果你想休产假
Well, if you want to take maternity leave...
哦  对啊
Oh, right.
我在这里  你知道的  可以做任何事
I'm here, you know, to do whatever.
好的  谢谢你
Well, thank you.
我想说的是  给我一些忠告
All I'm saying is, you know, give me some warning
因为我已经习惯了自由
because I've kinda gotten used to the free time.
我打算竞选市议会议员
I'm planning to run for City Council.
但你知道  随便什么
But, you know...whatever.
如果你需要我跟董事谈一谈  或者是放松一下
lf you need me to talk to the Board or take the reins back for awhile,
请告诉我
just let me know.
我打算呆在这儿  阿尔文
Well, I'm planning on staying here, Alvin...
长期的  你知道的  所以
for the long term, you know? So...
是的
Right.
我并不是说你会离开  露露
I'm not suggesting you weren't, Lulu.
是的
Right.
我为你感到高兴  露露
I'm happy for you, Lulu.
你和尼克  真的很高兴
You and Nick. Truly happy.
谢谢
Thanks.
今天你爸爸  呃  有一点盛气凌人
So, today your dad was, uh, a little condescending.
什么意思
What?
他问我以前是否处理过这样的索赔
Yeah, he asked me if I ever handled a claim like this before.
好吧  那你处理过呢
Well, have you?
这不是重点
That's not the point.
他告诉你我们的谈话了吗
Did he tell you about our conversation?
他说他去找你了
He said that he went to talk to you.
你告诉他我们的事了吗
Did you tell him about us?
怀孕的事吗  不  没有告诉他
About the pregnancy? No. No.
那求婚的事儿呢
What about the proposal?
嗯  你知道  我  呃
Well, you know, l, uh...
我确实向他要了我妈妈的戒指
I did ask him for my mother's ring.
那是你妈妈的戒指
That was your mother's ring?
是的
Yeah.
- 你没告诉过我这个  - 没关系的
- You didn't tell me that. - It doesn't matter.
你觉得你爸爸会讨厌我吗
Do you think maybe your dad resents me being--
不  这只是他做生意的方式
No, it's just the way he does business.
相信我
Believe me.
嘿
Hey.
你得让我离开那个基督教的收容所
You gotta get me out of that Christian men's shelter.
- 鲁弗斯  - 你得让我离开那里
- Rufus. - You gotta get me out of there.
那地方就像个监狱  一群动物在里面
lt's like a prison in that place, bunch a animals.
我从没问过你爸是怎么死的
You know, I never asked how your dad died.
抽烟
Smoking.
酗酒
Drinking.
我以前也和你爸爸一起喝过酒
I used to drink with your dad,
有时候晚上在码头上  然后  呃
down on the dock some nights and, uh...
伙计  他真的是很能喝
Man, he could really put it away.
但我也和他一起打球  你知道吗
But I played ball with him, too, you know?
我是说  他打球  而我坐冷板凳
I mean, he played and I rode the pine.
但有一场对阵辛雷的比赛  双加时赛
But there was this one game against Schenley, double overtime.
伙计  教练从来没有让他下场
Man! Coach never took him out.
无论辛雷做什么  他们都无法阻止鲍比
And no matter what Schenley did, they couldn't stop Bobby.
我过去常和他在车道上玩篮球
I used to play hoops with him in the driveway.
当然  他只用一只手投篮
Of course he only shot one-handed
因为他另一只手里总是拿着啤酒瓶
because he always had a beer bottle in the other.
阿尔文  我想了很多
Alvin, I've been thinking a lot.
我一直在想  如果我不喝酒
And I've been thinking maybe if I stopped with the drinking,
我可以去你说的那个地方
I could go to that place you were talking about...
如果我不喝酒的话
if I stopped.
你好
Hello?
啊  道恩
Ah, Dawn.
阿尔文·马斯特森  听着  有一位先生和我在一起
Alvin Masterson. Listen, I have a gentleman here with me
他正在处理一些问题  但是
who has some issues he's working on but, uh...
我认为他在休利特公寓可能会成功
I think that he may succeed at Hewlett House.
嗯 我可以等
Yeah, I can hold.
唷
Whew.
如果隆戈先生放弃这一不利占有要求
lf Mr. Longo will drop this adverse possession claim,
哈西先生愿意在多尔蒙给他一套公寓
Mr. Hassey is willing to give him an apartment in Dormont.
- 多尔蒙  - 是的
- Dormont? - Yeah.
那不是一个很好的社区
That's not a very nice neighborhood.
比他现在住的地方好多了
Well, it's a lot better than where he's living now.
是的  但这片土地可能价值70万美元
Yeah, but the land in question is potentially worth $700,000.
多尔蒙的一居室公寓还不到4万美元
And a one-bedroom apartment in Dormont is worth less than forty.
我们谈话的唯一原因
The only reason we're having this conversation
因为我的客户想开始他的开发建设  但现在
is because my client wants to start construction on his development... now.
如果你跟我提起诉讼
And if you litigate this thing with me,
你的委托人最终什么也得不到
your client's gonna end up receiving nothing.
而且你会浪费很多宝贵的时间
And you're gonna be wasting a lot of your valuable time
那本可以献给真正需要你的人
that could've been dedicated to people who really need you.
拉尔夫·隆戈的福利记录显示
Ralph Longo's welfare records came in.
20多年来  他一直在领取食品券
He's been receiving food stamps for over two decades,
他的地址也一直在上面
and his listed address for that entire time
就是你把他赶出去的那栋房子
is the house that you evicted him from.
难道不是吗
ls that a no?
我会把你的报价带给我的客户  但我不会建议他接受的
I'll bring your offer to my client, but I'm not gonna recommend it.
好吧
Okay.
是啊  好的
Yeah, okay.
呃  我们以后再谈
Uh, I guess I'll talk to you later.
好的  保重
Yeah, okay. Take care.
钢人队的传球防守再次失败
''The Steelers' pass defense failed again.
唯一的亮点是他们三重奏组合
''The only bright spot was their receiving trio
总共进攻了300码
which combined for 300 yards in total offense.''
嘿  爷爷  你在听吗
Hey, Gramps. You listening?
哦  对不起
Oh, sorry.
我只是累了
I'm just tired.
- 寄养家庭怎么说  - 他们会带走他的
- What'd the foster family say? - They'll take him.
你有把其他孩子送到那儿去过吗
You've sent other kids there?
他们专门针对高危青少年  他们非常好
They specialize in at-risk teens. They're very good.
他们在一起很好  你知道吗
They're great together, you know?
嘿
Hey!
你看他的病历了吗
Have you even looked at his chart?
他对花生酱过敏  你这个混蛋
He's allergic to peanut butter, you jackass!
对不起
Sorry.
我很抱歉  你能不能替他拿些火鸡来  拜托了
I'm sorry. Can you please just get him some turkey instead? Please?
好孩子
Good boy.
有一个寄养家庭
There's a foster family--
不  我不去
No. No.
唐尼  你不能一直住一个庇护所
Donnie, you can't stay in a shelter forever.
我不会的
I'm not going to.
祖父说他的律师会处理一切
Grandpa says his lawyer's gonna take care of everything,
然后我们会得到一些钱
and then we're gonna get some money.
隆戈先生  社会服务部门发现给唐尼找到一个非常好的寄养家庭
Mr. Longo, Social Services has found Donnie a very good foster home.
好吧  我会告诉法庭  我认为对你来说是最好的地方
Well, I'm gonna tell the court I think it's the best place for you.
听着  多亏了你  我每天只有两个小时可以和祖父在一起
Look, thanks to you, I only get two hours a day with my grandfather,
然后你还要减少它
and you're cutting into it.
嘿  你是要参加竞选吗
Hey, you running for something?
- 认真想一想  传单不错  很有创意
- Thinking about it. - Nice flyers. Very creative.
谢谢您
Thanks.
市议会  令人印象深刻
City Council. Impressive.
天哪  伙计  我会投给像你这样的人
Hell, man, I'd vote for a guy like you.
给你
Here.
- 这都是什么  肥皂  洗发水  剃须刀
- What's all this? - Soap. Shampoo. Razor.
沿街有地方  去把自己弄干净
There's a ''Y'' down the street. Go get yourself cleaned up.
给你
Here you go.
是的  这些应该正合适
Yeah, these should fit.
你必须要给人留下好的印象
You have to make a good impression
在今天下午的休利特公寓的面试中
at your Hewlett House interview this afternoon.
休利特公寓
Hewlett House?
是的  今天早上都确认了  他们会和你见面的
Yeah, confirmed everything this morning. They'll meet with you.
好吧  非常感谢  伙计
All right. Thanks a lot, man.
- 这是我的荣幸  - 待会儿见
- My pleasure. - I'll see you later.
是啊
Yeah.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我就在附近  我想我应该顺便来拜访一下
Yeah, I was just in the neighborhood. I thought I'd drop by for a second.
- 好啊  - 是的
- Okay. - Yeah.
所以这是新的办公室吗
So this is a new office, right?
- 是的  - 这里很好
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
你觉得管理这个地方怎么样
How do you like running this place?
- 是的  我可以的  - 好的  好的
- Yeah, I do. - Good. Good.
我能为你做些什么  伯顿?
What can I do for you, Burton?
我想知道你会不会让你的客户接受我们的报价
I was just wondering if you got a chance to take our offer to your client.
他对这个不感兴趣
He wasn't interested.
哦
Oh.
好吧  那公寓在加一万美金呢
Well, suppose we put the 10,OOO on top of the apartment?
再说一次  我会建议我的委托人不要接受的
Again, I would recommend that my client not take it.
现在你知道这是我们的最终报价了  是吗
Now you do know this is our final offer, right?
是的  伯顿  我只是想再说一下
Right. Burton, I just wanted to mention that, you know,
尼克和我正在想我们的事
Nick and I are trying to figure things out.
但是我感到非常荣幸  当我发现戒指来自于哪里时
But I was very honored when I found out that the ring came from--
这个  我想那是你和尼克之间的事
Well, I guess that's between you and Nick.
是的
Right.
那么  我们法庭见
So, I guess I'll see you in court.
保重
Take care.
那就这样吧
There you go.
哦  谢谢你借给我
Oh, thanks for the loaner.
这是我男朋友的领带
lt's my boyfriend's tie.
嘿  真有你的
Hey, good for you.
像你这样漂亮的女孩  生活中就应该有一个好男人
Pretty girl like you should have a nice fella in her life.
嗯  你戴着它看起来很帅
Well, you look very handsome in it.
谢谢
Thanks.
你让我想起一个人
You know, you remind me of someone.
是的  很久以前  我有过一个女孩
Yeah. I had a girl once, long time ago.
漂亮  不过没有你漂亮
Pretty. Not so pretty as you, though.
我  我对她不好  一点也不好
I I didn't treat her well not so good at all.
这是不对的  我应该对她好一点  但是
That was a mistake. I should have treated her better but...
不管怎样  你让我想起了她
Anyway, you remind me of her.
- 你准备好了吗  - 是的
- You ready? - Yeah.
走吧
Here you go.
好的
Okay.
- 你没事吧  - 没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
- 你确定吗  - 是的
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
- 你知道的  你不必过来的  - 不  我想去
- You know, you don't have to come. - No, I want to go.
我是说  没有你我也可以的  我有你的资料
I mean, I can do it without you. I've got your amidavits.
我想去  谢谢
I want to go. Thanks.
- 可以吗  - 可以
- Okay? - Okay.
雷·施米尔在他清醒的时候努力工作
Ray Schmiel works hard at his sobriety.
就像所有的瘾君子一样  他有他的缺点  但他在努力
Like all addicts, he has his lapses, but he's trying,
他想要成功
and he wants to succeed.
我知道他会从休利特公寓获益
I know that he'll benefit from being at Hewlett House,
但是休利特公寓也将从他的加盟中获益
but Hewlett House will benefit from having him.
阿尔文  施米尔先生仍然在喝酒
Alvin, Mr. Schmiel is still drinking.
他会停止的
He's gonna stop.
你知道我们这里的政策
You know our policy here.
政策是很好
And it's a good one.
但我知道你能帮助他
But I know you can help him.
道恩  如果我不相信的话  我不会让你这么做的
Dawn, I wouldn't ask you to do this if I didn't believe that.
欢迎你  施米尔先生
Welcome, Mr. Schmiel.
好的
All right.
- 嘿  露露  - 嗨  伯顿
- Hey, Lulu. - Hi, Burton.
隆戈先生
Mr. Longo.
爸爸  露露  呃  有点问题  我们得推迟听证会
Dad, Lulu, uh, there's a bit of a problem. We need to adjourn the hearing.
- 我们就要开始了  - 有什么问题吗
- We're just about to get started. - What's the problem?
是关于唐尼的
lt's about Donnie.
- 发生了什么事  - 不能等一下吗
- What happened? - Can't it wait?
爸爸  请你休庭一周好吗
Dad, can you just ask for a week's adjournment, please?
唐尼在试图取回12袋冰毒时被捕了
Donnie was caught trying to retrieve 12 bags of crystal meth
从老房子的壁炉里
from the fireplace in his old house.
从我们的房子吗
From our house?
你知道你家里有毒品吗
Did you know there were drugs in your house?
什么都别说了  隆戈先生
Don't say anything, Mr. Longo.
他和公设辩护人谈过了吗
Has he spoken to a public defender yet?
他会被传讯的
He'll get one at arraignment.
还有更多的
There's more.
唐尼的真名是门德斯
Donnie's real last name is Mendez.
他在10岁时与印第安纳州韦恩堡的家人失散
He's been missing from his family in Fort Wayne, Indiana, since he was ten.
什么
What?
在幼儿园之前  他的指纹就被记录了
Turns out he was finger-printed before nursery school.
所以当警察采集他的指纹时
So when the police ran his prints--
已经通知他的母亲了
His mother's been notified.
你查过了没
Did you check her out?
冰毒吗
Meth?
我要赚更多的钱
I had to make some more cash
这样我们就可以出城找个地方住了
so we could get out of town and find some place to live.
老拉尔夫不是你的祖父
And old Ralph isn't your grandfather.
嗯  他总是说如果他有一个孙子  他肯定会像我一样
Well, he always said if he had a grandson, he'd bet he'd be like me.
我曾经开玩笑地叫过他祖父  他很喜欢
I called him Gramps once as a joke and he liked it.
你们什么时候认识的
When did you two hook up?
四年前我刚到匹兹堡的时候
Four years ago when I first got to Pittsburgh.
拉尔夫看到我被一些年龄较大的孩子欺负了
Ralph saw me getting my ass kicked by some older kids,
他赶走了他们  所以
and he chased them off, so...
我被打得很惨  他说我可以留下来
I was pretty beat-up, and he said I could stay.
他从来没有让我离开
He never asked me to go.
拉尔夫知道你在他家里卖毒品吗
Did Ralph know you were selling drugs out of his house?
当然不知道
Of course not.
你说的是实话吗
You telling me the truth?
如果他知道  他会杀了我
He'd kill me if he knew.
但我不得不赚钱
But I had to to make some money.
拉尔夫无法工作
Ralph couldn't work.
如果我不和他在一起  他撑不了一年的
lf I'm not with him, he won't last a year.
如果我进监狱的话  他会怎么样
What's gonna happen to him if I go to jail?
谁来照顾他
Who's gonna take care of him?
在对他的刑事指控尚未处理之前
Pending disposition of the criminal charges against him,
唐纳德·门德斯的监护权要立刻回到他母亲手上
Donald Mendez is to be returned immediately to his mother's custody.
唐尼
Donnie!
我从未停止过祈祷  我从未停止过
I never stopped praying. I never stopped.
他们要带唐尼去哪里
Where are they taking Donnie?
他的公设辩护人提出了申辩
His public defender worked out a plea.
他将在韦恩堡服缓刑
He's gonna be serving his probation in Fort Wayne.
但是他们要把他带到哪里去
But where are they taking him?
他要回印第安纳州与他的妈妈住在一起
He's going back to Indiana to live with his mom.
来吧  我带你回医院
Come on. I'm going to take you back to the hospital.
他告诉我他没有家人了
He told me he had no family.
他说他一直都在流浪
He said he was living on the street his whole life.
休利特公寓今天早上打电话给我了
Hewlett House called me this morning.
他们把我赶出去了  你得给我找一个新地方了
They threw me out. You got to find me a new place.
他们发现你在吸毒
They found you doing meth.
是的
Yeah.
你说过你会保持清白的
You said you were gonna stay clean.
别提了  伙计  我们都不干净
Come on, man! None of us are clean.
你觉得超级流浪汉是干净的吗  他现在很兴奋
You think Super Bum is clean? He's high right now.
得了  别那么惊讶
Come on now! Don't look so so surprised.
我在你的电梯里买了冰毒
I bought the meth on your elevator
从我身边的一个孩子那里
from one of the kids that lives on the lot from me.
看  阿尔文  我搞砸了
Look, Alvin, I slipped up.
给休利特公司打电话吧  再给我一次机会
Just call Hewlett House. Give me another chance.
你老爸会帮助我的
Your old man would have helped me.
有一次  我在酒吧后面晕了过去
This one time, I passed out behind the bar
有两个家伙想把我打翻
and these two guys tried to roll me,
然后鲍比出来了
and Bobby comes out of--
我昨天去了奥尔德里奇高中
I went to Aldrich High School yesterday.
我父亲从没有在高中打过球
My dad never played senior year.
他从来没有做过校队
He never even made varsity.
我参加了一个新赛季的比赛
I Half a season freshman ball that was it.
不过  你打了
You played, though.
队长  赛季的最有价值球员
Team captain. Season MVP
你打了两场加时赛
You played that double-overtime game.
嘿  听着
Hey, look--
你也替那孩子挨打了吗
Did you take the paddling for that kid, too?
是啊  是我被打了
Yeah, I'm the one that got paddled.
离开我的办公室
Just get out of my office.
我告诉了你  你想听的
I told you what I thought you wanted to hear.
好吧  休利特公寓现在是不可能了
Well, Hewlett House is out of the question now.
那就去别的地方吧
Well, someplace else then.
我会去打几个电话
I'll make a few calls.
好的
All right.
我们在月底有一个募捐活动
We have a fundraiser scheduled for the end of the month,
并打电话让你进入匹兹堡政坛
and I made some calls to get you onto Pittsburgh politics.
我以为你拒绝了
I thought you were Ieaning towards no.
我是拒绝了  但我想了想你说的话
I was. But then I thought about what you said,
关于你的经历  你和穷人的合作
about your experience, your work with the poor.
你有良好的意愿  阿尔文
You got good intensions, Alvin.
很美好  没有其他的了
lt's sweet, nothing else.
谢谢
Thank you... I think.
嗯  我得走了
Well, gotta run.
我稍后会打电话给你  讨论安排一些辩论
I'll call you later to talk about setting up some debates.
好的
Okay.
那是什么
What's that stuff?
一个改变的机会  小罗伯特
An opportunity for change, young Robert.
一个改变的机会
An opportunity of a change.
唐尼的妈妈开车送他回家的途中
Donnie's mother was driving him home.
在第一次红灯时  他跳了出来  来到了这里
At the first red light, he jumps out and comes here.
发生了什么事
What happened?
想和拉尔夫一起走  但他们甚至没能穿过走廊
He tried to leave with Ralph, but they didn't even make it down the hallway.
- 唐尼在哪儿  - 他在这里
- Where's Donnie? - He's here.
唐尼
Donnie!
什么  什么
What--what.. .
他会怎么样
What's gonna happen to him?
他的缓刑将被撤销
His probation will be revoked,
他将因持有毒品而服刑
and he'll have to serve the sentence for drug possession.
- 如果它们是我的毒品呢  - 隆戈先生
- What if they were my drugs? - Mr. Longo--
如果毒品是我的  唐尼就不会进监狱了
Donnie can't go to prison for drugs if they were mine.
他卖毒品是为了我  这样我们就有钱了
He was selling them for me so we'd have money.
你说的是很严重的  隆戈先生
What you're saying is very serious, Mr. Longo.
请你给我一点时间好吗
Will you give me a minute, please?
听着  我知道你是想帮忙  但你只会把事情弄得更糟
Listen, I know you're trying to help, but you're just gonna make things worse.
拜托  安静点  好吗  请给我一点时间
Please, just be quiet, okay? Just give me a minute.
你知道他不是那个意思
You know he didn't mean that.
我的意思是你有道德义务
What I mean is that you have an ethical obligation
对他说的话保密
to keep what he said to yourself.
- 为什么  - 因为这是机密信息
Why? - Because it's privileged information.
拉尔夫不是我的委托人
Ralph isn't my client.
你为LSP工作  他是LSP的委托人  他是你的委托人
You work for LSP. He's an LSP client. He's your client.
哦  别这样  露露  你听到了  我也听到了
Oh, come on, Lulu. You heard it. I heard it.
他公开承认使用这片地产是为了犯罪
He publicly admitted to using that property for criminal purpose.
这就否定了他的逆权占有要求
That kills his adverse possession claim.
他只是一个保护他所爱男孩的老人
He's just an old man who's protecting a boy that he loves.
别这样  尼克
Come on, Nick.
而且  它是保密的
Besides, it's privileged.
好吧
Okay.
我很高兴你说服了客户  这是一笔好的交易
Well, I'm glad you convinced your client this is a good deal.
- 嗯  有道理  - 是啊
- Well, it made sense. - Yeah.
我来起草公寓的文件
I'll draw up the papers for the apartment
下个星期  我会寄给你一张1万美元的支票  好吗
and then next week, I'll send you a cashier's check for $10,000, okay?
- 好的  谢谢  - 你说对了  谢谢
- Okay. Thank you. - You bet. Thank you.
- 嗨  - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
呃  我在办公室还有一些工作要完成  我们在家见面
Uh, I have some work to finish up at the office. I'll see you at home?
- 好啊  - 好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
- 再见  - 再见  保重
- Bye. - Bye. Take care.
你跟她谈过这件事吗
Did you talk to her about this?
没有
No.
她就这样改变主意了
She just changed her mind?
嗯  我想是的
Well, I guess.
这对哈西来说是个好买卖
This is a good deal for Hassey.
大家都知道  那位年轻女士打赢了案子
Truth be known, that young lady had a winning case.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
嘿  那纳马柯林呢  我们还去吗
Hey, what about Namacolin? Are we still on?
当然
Sure.
你会带露露来吗
Are you gonna bring Lulu?
你问过她吗
Have you even asked her yet?
我还没抽出时间来
I haven't gotten around to it yet.
尼古拉斯  问她  带她过来  好吗
Nicholas, ask her. Bring her, okay?
这样对你有好处  好吗
lt'll be good for you, okay?
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我刚跟劳里谈了谈
I just spoke to Laurie.
她将在明天开设唐尼的犯罪听证会
She's gonna set up Donnie's delinquency hearing for tomorrow.
是的  她已经打电话给我了
Yeah, she already called.
我一直在想唐尼的妈妈
You know, I can't stop thinking about Donnie's mother.
我是说  当你的儿子还是个小男孩的时候
I mean, you lose your son when he's a little boy,
你花了很多年寻找他  想知道他是否还活着
you spend years looking for him, wondering if he's even alive.
然后有一天  突然  电话响了
And then one day, out of the blue, the phone rings.
当她看到他的时候
And when she sees him, I mean, you know,
他不再是个孩子了  他是个男人了
he's not a kid anymore, he's a man.
不再像她丢失的那个男孩
Couldn't possibly resemble the boy she lost.
现在她又要失去他了
And now she's gonna lose him again.
许多父母辜负了他们的孩子
So many parents fail their children.
是啊
Yeah.
做错误的决定似乎很容易
It just seems so easy to make all the wrong decisions.
好吧  我想你只要尽力就行了
Well, I guess you just got to do the best you can.
是啊
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
你只是在这里看到了错误的决定
You only ever see the wrong decisions here.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177